Finding Aid for School of Public Health (University of Michigan) Records 1909-2015 (bulk 1941-2006).
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean Myron E. Wegman, 1958-1973
  - Annual Files, 1967
    - Administration
      - Continuing Education Service, 1967 (Box 17)
      - Library, 1967 (Box 17)
      - Memoranda (department heads), 1967 (Box 17)
      - Memoranda (faculty), 1967 (Box 17)
      - Students, 1967 (Box 17)
    - American Public Health Association
      - Annual Meeting (Miami), 1967 (Box 17)
      - Committee on Professional Education, 1967 (Box 17)
      - Executive Board, 1967; 2 folders (Box 17)
      - Legislation, 1967 (Box 17)
      - Task Force on Institutions of Higher Learning, 1965-1967 (Box 17)
    - Committees
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Rank, 1967 (Box 17)
      - Advisory Committee on Research, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
      - Continuing Education, 1967 (Box 17)
      - Executive, 1967 (Box 17)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1967 (Box 17)
      - Instruction, 1967; 2 folders (Box 17)
      - Policy on Population Planning, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
      - Scholarship, 1967 (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, 1967; 6 folders (Box 18)
    - Departments/Divisions
      - Biostatistics, 1967 (Box 18)
      - Community Health (V. Getting), 1967
        - Public Health Nursing, 1967 (Box 18)
      - Environmental Health (M. Hilbert and J. Gannon), 1967; 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Epidemiology (T. Francis), 1967 (Box 18)
      - Health Development (P. O'Connor, M. Rugen, and D. Smith), 1967; 3 folders (Box 18)
      - Industrial Health, 1967 (Box 18)
      - Medical Care Organization (S. Axelrod), 1967 (Box 18)
      - Population Planning Center (L. Corsa), 1967 (Box 18)
  - Annual Files, 1968
    - Administration
      - General, 1968 (Box 18)
      - Annual Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 18)
      - Memoranda (department heads), 1967-1968 (Box 18)
      - Memoranda (faculty), 1968 (Box 18)
      - Students, 1968
        - Disruptive Activities Policy, 1968 (Box 18)
    - American Public Health Association
      - General, 1968 (Box 18)
      - Committee on Professional Education, 1968 (Box 18)
      - Executive Board, 1967-1968 (Box 18)
      - Legislation, 1968 (Box 18)
    - Committees
      - General, 1967-1968 (Box 18)
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Rank, 1968 (Box 18)
      - Computer, 1968 (Box 18)
      - Continuing Education and Community Relations, 1968 (Box 18)
      - "Corsa" (re teaching), 1967-1968 (Box 18)
      - Executive, 1968 (Box 18)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1968 (Box 18)
      - Instruction, 1968 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence
      - January-June, 1968, 3 folders (Box 18)
      - July-December, 1968, 3 folders (Box 19)
    - Departments/Divisions
      - Biostatistics (F. Moore), 1968 (Box 19)
      - Bureau of Hospital Administration (L. Hill and E. Helt), 1968; 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Community Health, 1968 (Box 19)
      - Environmental Health, 1968
        - Water Quality Control, 1968-1969 (Box 19)
      - Epidemiology, 1968
        - Research Center for Diseases of the Heart, 1968 (Box 19)
      - Health Development (L. Baler, J. Robson, M. Rugen, and D. Smith), 1968; 4 folders (Box 19)
      - Medical Care Organization (S. Axelrod), 1968 (Box 19)
      - Population Planning Center (L. Corsa), 1967-1968 (Box 19)
  - Annual Files, 1969
    - Administration
      - General, 1969 (Box 19)
      - Annual Reports, 1968-1969; 3 folders (Box 19)
      - Memoranda (department heads), 1969 (Box 19)
      - Memoranda (faculty), 1969 (Box 19)
      - Students, 1969
        - Public Health Club, 1968-1969 (Box 19)
    - American Public Health Association
      - General, 1968-1969 (Box 19)
      - Committee on Professional Education, 1969 (Box 19)
      - Conference on Health of Youth, 1969 (Box 19)
      - Executive Board, 1969; 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Legislation, 1969 (Box 19)
    - Committees
      - General, 1969 (Box 19)
      - Advisory Committee on Health Planning, 1969 (Box 19)
      - Continuing Education, 1969 (Box 19)
      - Instruction, 1969 (Box 19)
      - Search (Epidemiology-Francis), 1969 (Box 19)
      - Search (Industrial Health-Magnuson), 1969 (Box 19)
    - Correspondence, 1969; 6 folders (Box 20)
    - Departments/Divisions
      - Biostatistics (F. Moore), 1969 (Box 20)
      - Community Health, 1969 (Box 20)
      - Environmental Health, 1969 (Box 20)
      - Epidemiology, 1969
        - Research Center for Diseases of the Heart, 1964-1969 (Box 20)
      - Health Development (L. Baler, J. Robson, and D. Striffler), 1968-1969; 3 folders (Box 20)
      - Hospital Administration (L. Hill), 1969 (Box 20)
      - Industrial Health (Dinman), 1968-1969 (Box 20)
      - Medical Care Organization (S. Axelrod), 1969 (Box 20)
      - Population Planning Center (L. Corsa), 1969 (Box 20)
  - Annual Files, 1970
    - Administration
      - General, 1970 (Box 20)
      - Annual Reports, 1969-1970; 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Building, 1963-1970; 3 folders (Box 20)
      - Memoranda (department heads), 1970 (Box 20)
      - Memoranda (faculty), 1970 (Box 20)
      - Students (Discipline), 1970 (Box 20)
    - American Public Health Association
      - General, 1970 (Box 20)
      - Committee on Professional Education, 1970 (Box 20)
      - Executive Board, 1970 (Box 20)
      - Legislation, 1970 (Box 20)
    - Committees
      - General, 1969-1970 (Box 20)
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Rank, 1970 (Box 20)
      - Advisory Committee on Research, 1969-1970 (Box 20)
      - Computer, 1970 (Box 20)
      - Continuing Education/Extension, 1970 (Box 20)
      - Instruction, 1970 (Box 20)
      - Search (Hospital Administration), 1969-1970 (Box 20)
    - Correspondence, 1970; 6 folders (Box 21)
    - Departments/Divisions
      - Environmental and Industrial Health, 1970 (Box 21)
      - Epidemiology (F. Epstein), 1970
        - Research Center for Diseases of the Heart (Box 21)
      - Health Development, 1970; 3 folders (Box 21)
      - Hospital Administration (J. Griffith), 1970 (Box 21)
      - Medical Care Organization (Feingold), 1970 (Box 21)
      - Population Planning Center (L. Corsa), 1970 (Box 21)
  - Annual Files, 1971
    - Administration
      - General, 1971 (Box 21)
      - Annual Reports, 1970-1971; 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Building (Dedication), 1970-1971 (Box 21)
      - Library, 1971 (Box 21)
      - Memoranda (department heads), 1971 (Box 21)
      - Memoranda (faculty), 1971 (Box 21)
      - Photographs, 1965-1970 (Box 21)
      - Students, 1970-1971 (Box 21)
    - American Public Health Association
      - General, 1971 (Box 21)
      - Annual Meeting (Minneapolis), 1971 (Box 21)
      - Executive Board, 1970-1971 (Box 21)
    - Committees
      - General, 1971 (Box 21)
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Rank, 1971 (Box 21)
      - Advisory Committee on Research, 1971 (Box 21)
      - Audiovisual, 1970-1971 (Box 21)
      - Computer, 1971 (Box 21)
      - Development, 1970-1971 (Box 21)
      - Executive, 1969-1971 (Box 21)
    - Correspondence
      - 1971, 6 folders (Box 21)
    - Departments/Divisions
      - Biostatistics (F. Moore), 1970-1971 (Box 21)
      - Community Health (V. Getting), 1971 (Box 21)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health (M. Hilbert), 1969-1971; 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Epidemiology (F. Davenport), 1971
        - Research Center for Diseases of the Heart (Box 21)
      - Health Development (Baler, Robson, Simonds, and D. Smith), 1971; 4 folders (Box 22)
      - Hospital Administration (J. Griffith), 1971 (Box 22)
      - Medical Care Organization (Feingold), 1971
        - Search for Chairman, 1970-1971 (Box 22)
      - Population Planning Center (L. Corsa), 1971 (Box 22)
  - Annual Files, 1972
    - Administration
      - General, 1972 (Box 22)
      - Annual Reports, 1971-1972; 2 folders (Box 22)
      - Memoranda (department heads), 1972 (Box 22)
      - Memoranda (faculty), 1972 (Box 22)
      - Public Health Alumni Society, 1972 (Box 22)
      - Students, 1972 (Box 22)
    - American Public Health Association
      - President Myron Wegman, 1972 (Box 22)
      - Annual Meeting (Atlantic City), 1972 (Box 22)
      - Committee on Professional Education, 1972 (Box 22)
      - Executive Board, 1972 (Box 22)
      - "The Nation's Health" Column, 1971-1972 (Box 22)
    - Committees
      - General, 1972 (Box 22)
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Rank, 1972 (Box 22)
      - Advisory Committee on Research, 1972 (Box 22)
      - Computer (Advisory), 1971-1972 (Box 22)
      - Development, 1972 (Box 22)
      - Executive, 1972 (Box 22)
      - Instruction, 1972 (Box 22)
    - Correspondence
      - 1972, 6 folders (Box 22)
    - Departments/Divisions
      - Biostatistics (R. Cornell), 1972 (Box 22)
      - Community Health (V. Getting), 1972 (Box 22)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health, 1972 (Box 22)
      - Epidemiology (F. Davenport), 1972
        - Research Center for Diseases of the Heart (Box 22)
      - Health Development, 1968-1972; 2 folders (Box 22)
      - Medical Care Organization (Feingold), 1972 (Box 22)
      - Population Planning Center (L. Corsa), 1972 (Box 22)
  - Annual Files, 1973
    - Administration
      - General, 1973 (Box 23)
      - Annual Reports, 1972-1973; 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Library, 1973 (Box 23)
      - Memoranda (department heads), 1973 (Box 23)
      - Memoranda (faculty), 1973 (Box 23)
      - Public Health Alumni Society, 1973 (Box 23)
      - Students, 1973 (Box 23)
      - Task Forces
        - Administrative Services, 1973 (Box 23)
        - Mission and Curriculum, 1973 (Box 23)
        - Research, 1973 (Box 23)
        - Service/Continuing Education, 1973 (Box 23)
        - Teaching, 1973 (Box 23)
    - American Public Health Association
      - General, 1973 (Box 23)
      - Committee on Professional Education, 1973 (Box 23)
      - Executive Board, 1973 (Box 23)
    - Committees
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Rank, 1973 (Box 23)
      - Advisory Committee on Research, 1973 (Box 23)
      - Advisory Council (formerly Development), 1973 (Box 23)
      - Affirmative Action for Women, 1971-1973 (Box 23)
      - Executive, 1973; 3 folders (Box 23)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1973 (Box 23)
      - Search (Dean), 1973 (Box 23)
    - Correspondence
      - 1973, 6 folders (Box 23)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics (R. Cornell), 1973 (Box 24)
      - Community Health (V. Getting), 1973 (Box 24)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health (M. Hilbert), 1973 (Box 24)
      - Epidemiology, 1973
        - Research Center for Diseases of the Heart (Box 24)
      - Medical Care Organization (Feingold), 1973 (Box 24)
      - Population Planning Center (L. Corsa), 1973 (Box 24)
    - Programs
      - Community Mental Health (L. Baler), 1973 (Box 24)
      - Dental Public Health (D. Striffler), 1973 (Box 24)
      - Health Behavior (I. Rosenstock), 1973 (Box 24)
      - Health Education (S. Simonds), 1973 (Box 24)
      - Health Planning, 1973 (Box 24)
      - Hospital Administration (J. Griffith), 1973 (Box 24)
      - Maternal and Child Health (S. Chipman), 1973 (Box 24)
      - Nutrition (J. Robson), 1973 (Box 24)
      - Public Health Nursing (L. Ostrand), 1973 (Box 24)
- Office Files, 1940-2005
  - Files, 1940-1978
    The subseries, Office Files; 1940-1978, comprises twelve linear feet and consists of diverse materials evidently used or stored as reference files. These records are arranged alphabetically by type of material and office of origin into four sub-subseries: Budgets, Committees, Core Course, and PBB Study. As with the Dean's files, these records pertain to both the internal workings of the School of Public Health (Budgets, Committees, and Core Course) and to the school's activities at the state (PBB Study) and national (Association of Schools of Public Health) levels
    - Budgets, 1940-1965
      The Budgets sub-subseries runs nearly 1.8 linear feet in Boxes 41 and 42 and provides detailed evidence of the financial operations of the school between 1940 and 1965. The relative importance of federal and foundation support is manifest in these records and the assessment of merit of individual faculty members is also revealed.
      - 1940 (Box 41)
        (Proposed)
      - 1941-1942
        - W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1941-1942 (Box 41)
        - USPHS Traineeship, 1941-1942 (Box 41)
      - 1942-1943
        - USPHS Traineeship, 1942-1943 (Box 41)
      - 1943-1944 (Box 41)
      - 1944-1945 (Box 41)
      - 1945-1946 (Box 41)
      - 1946-1947 (Box 41)
      - 1947-1948
        - Departmental, 1947-1948 (Box 41)
      - 1948-1949 (Box 41)
      - 1949-1950 (Box 41)
      - 1950-1951 (Box 41)
      - 1951-1952 (Box 41)
      - 1952-1953 (Box 41)
      - 1953-1954 (Box 41)
      - 1954-1955 (Box 41)
      - 1955-1956 (Box 41)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 41)
      - 1957-1958, 2 folders (Box 41)
      - 1958-1959, 2 folders
        - USPHS Traineeship, 1958-1959 (Box 41)
      - 1959-1960, 2 folders
        - USPHS Traineeship, 1959-1960 (Box 42)
      - 1960-1961, 2 folders
        - Departmental and Preliminary, 1960-1961 (Box 42)
        - USPHS Traineeship, 1960-1961 (Box 42)
      - 1961-1962
        - USPHS Traineeship, 1961-1962 (Box 42)
      - 1962-1963
        - Departments, 1962-1963 (Box 42)
        - Promotions and Merit Increases, 1962-1963 (Box 42)
        - USPHS Traineeship, 1962-1963 (Box 42)
      - 1963-1964
        - Departments, 1963-1964 (Box 42)
        - Promotions and Merit Increases, 1963-1964 (Box 42)
      - 1964-1965, 2 folders (Box 42)
      - Summaries of Accounts, 1964-1965 (Box 42)
    - Committees
      The Committees sub-subseries can be seen as duplicating similar materials in the dean's files. Here, however, the records of the Committee on Instruction and the Curriculum Committee are most complete in thoroughly documenting the basic issue of education at the school. Additional committee files are located in the various Deans' series
      - Curriculum Review (includes Penchansky Report), 1971-1974; 4 folders (Box 42)
      - Instruction, 1945-1974
        - Undated (Box 43)
        - Memoranda, 1945-1957 (Box 43)
        - 1947 (Box 43)
        - 1948-1949 (Box 43)
        - 1952 (Box 43)
        - 1953 (Box 43)
        - 1954 (Box 43)
        - 1955 (Box 43)
        - 1956 (Box 43)
        - 1957 (Box 43)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 43)
        - 1960 (Box 43)
        - 1961-1962 (Box 43)
        - 1963 (Box 43)
        - 1964 (Box 43)
        - 1965 (Box 43)
        - Memoranda, 1958-1965 (Box 43)
        - 1966 (Box 43)
        - 1967, 3 folders (Box 43)
        - 1968, 2 folders (Box 44)
        - 1969, 2 folders (Box 44)
        - 1970, 2 folders (Box 44)
        - 1971, 3 folders (Box 44)
        - 1972, 2 folders (Box 44)
        - 1973, 2 folders (Box 44)
        - 1974, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Core Courses
      Similarly the Core Course sub-subseries offers important evidence on the changing expectations and mores in public health education at a time when student unrest and dissent was at its height at the university. The Core Course sub-subseries provides a unique insight into what actually went on within the classrooms as a professional school strived to balance the demands of its students for relevance and dialogue with the needs of the professors and the school to preserve some semblance of professional training in a field growing increasingly complex and diverse.
      - Core Course Committee, 1965-1977
        - 1965 (Box 44)
        - 1966, 3 folders (Box 44)
        - 1967, 4 folders (Box 45)
        - 1968, 3 folders (Box 45)
        - 1969, 4 folders (Box 45)
        - 1970, 2 folders (Box 45)
        - 1971, 2 folders (Box 45)
        - 1972, 2 folders (Box 45)
          (Including Fairlane Conference)
        - 1973-1976, 2 folders (Box 45)
          (Including Core Review)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 45)
      - Teaching, 1966-1976
        - 1966-1967
          - Exams, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 46)
          - Lectures, 1966; 3 folders (Box 46)
          - Lecture Transcripts, 1966 (Box 46)
        - 1967-1968
          - Cases, 1967 (Box 46)
          - Exams, 1967-1968; 2 folders (Box 46)
          - Lectures, 1967-1968; 3 folders (Box 46)
          - Lecture Transcripts, 1967 (Box 46)
        - 1968-1969
          - Cases, 1969 (Box 46)
          - Exams, 1968-1969; 2 folders (Box 46)
          - Lectures, 1968-1969; 3 folders (Box 46)
        - 1969-1970
          - Cases, 1969-1970 (Box 46)
          - Exams, 1969-1970; 2 folders (Box 46)
          - Lectures, 1969-1970; 3 folders (Box 46)
        - 1970-1971
          - Cases, 1970-1971; 3 folders (Box 47)
          - Exams, 1970-1971; 2 folders (Box 47)
        - 1971-1972
          - Cases, 1971-1972; 2 folders (Box 47)
          - Exams, 1971-1972; 2 folders (Box 47)
          - Lectures, 1972 (Box 47)
        - 1972-1973
          - Cases, 1972-1973; 2 folders (Box 47)
          - Exams, 1972-1973 (Box 47)
          - Lectures, 1972-1973 (Box 47)
        - 1973-1974
          - Cases, 1973-1974; 2 folders (Box 47)
          - Exams, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
          - Lectures, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
        - 1974-1975
          - Cases, 1974-1975; 2 folders (Box 48)
          - Exams, 1974-1975 (Box 48)
          - Lectures, 1974-1975 (Box 48)
        - 1975-1976
          - Cases, 1975-1976; 2 folders (Box 48)
          - Exams, 1975-1976 (Box 48)
          - Lectures, 1975-1976 (Box 48)
    - PBB Study
      The other file dealing with external issues is the PBB Study; these materials run 0.6 linear feet in Box 48 and document the school's efforts to establish via epidemiological and biological evidence the far reaching implications of polybrominated biphenyls on human health.
      - Correspondence, 1977-1980; 8 folders (Box 48)
      - Protocols, 1978; 3 folders (Box 48)
      - Report (final), September 1978 (Box 48)
      - Testimony (Remington), 1977-1978 (Box 48)
  - Files, 1941-1991
    The Office Files, 1941-1992 subseries (primarily 1984-1989) consists of 4 linear feet of records organized into three sub-subseries: Center for Continuing Education of Public Health Professionals, Committees, and Departmental Reviews. The records in this subseries were maintained separately from the dean's annual files and have been retained in the manner in which they were received.
    - Center for Continuing Education of Public Health Professionals
      The Center for Continuing Education of Public Health Professionals sub-subseries consists of 0.4 linear feet dating from 1979 to 1984. The Center was funded for six years by a grant from the W. K. Kellogg Foundation. Records include executive board minutes, progress reports, and research reports regarding continuing education activities and needs assessments. Related documentation also appears in the annual files of each of the various deans.
      - Executive Board Meetings, 1979-1984; 4 folders (Box 48)
      - Grant Proposal for Continuation, 1981 (Box 48)
      - Progress Reports, 1979-1984; 2 folders (Box 48)
      - Reports
        - CHA Report 1 "Community Health Associate's Orientation and Continuing Education Program,", 1979 (Box 48)
        - CHA Report 2 "CHA Entry Mechanisms Established Time Plan of Activities,", 1979 (Box 48)
        - CHA Report 3 "CHA Site Visit Standardization Procedural Guidelines for Pre-Site, On-Site, and Post-Site Activities,", 1979 (Box 48)
        - CHA Report 4 "Information Packet for Distribution to Potential Clients During A Presentation,", 1979 (Box 48)
        - Continuing Education Needs Assessment/Market Analysis of Public Health Professionals in Michigan,", 1983 (Box 48)
        - Research Report 1 "Scope of Activities,", 1979 (Box 48)
        - Research Report 2 "History of Continuing Education at the University of Michigan School of Public Health: Program and Policy,", 1979 (Box 48)
        - Research Report 3 "Client-Centered Planning: A Multi-Disciplinary Perspective, Theory, Evidence, and Application for Continuing Education of Health Professionals,", 1979 (Box 48)
        - Research Report 4 "Elements in the Planning Process,", 1979 (Box 48)
        - Sixth Year Report, 1983-1984 (Box 48)
    - Committees
      The sub-subseries, Committees, 0.6 linear feet, contains the official set of Executive Committee minutes dating from the school's founding in 1941 through 1963. One notebook of Advisory Council Minutes (previously Development Committee), 1968-1978, is also included here. These minutes richly illustrate school-wide administrative issues and policy decisions. Scattered minutes and related material will also be found within the annual files in the dean's series.
      - Advisory Council Minutes, 1968-1978 (Box 52)
      - Executive Committee, 1941/42-1963, 19 folders (Box 52)
    - Departmental Reviews
      The Departmental Reviews sub-subseries consists of 2 linear feet of records dating from 1972 to 1987. The records reflect two major review cycles (1975-1976 and 1982-1983), when each department underwent review, and two lesser cycles when only select departments were reviewed (1985 and 1987). Documentation includes self-studies, reports of internal and external review committees, and occasional rebuttals to these reports. The reviews provide remarkable insight into the effectiveness of the school and the individual departments in meeting educational goals and objectives while also anticipating future trends.
      - Review Committee, 1972-1982; 2 folders (Box 53)
      - Review Cycle, 1975-1976
        - Biostatistics, 1976-1978 (Box 53)
        - Community Health Programs, 1978-1979; 2 folders (Box 53)
        - Environmental and Industrial Health, 1975-1976; 2 folders (Box 53)
        - Epidemiology (includes review and search committee material), 1975-1976 (Box 53)
        - Health Behavior/Health Education, 1978-1980; 2 folders (Box 53)
        - Health Planning and Administration, 1978-1979 (Box 53)
        - Hospital Administration, 1976-1978 (Box 53)
        - Medical Care Organization, 1976-1978 (Box 53)
        - Population Planning (includes material re: discontinuance), 1975-1977; 3 folders (Box 53)
      - Review Cycle, 1982
        - Biostatistics, 1981-1982; 2 folders (Box 53)
        - Community Health Programs, 1983-1984
          - Child and Family Health Program, 1983 (Box 53)
          - Community Mental Health Program, 1983 (Box 53)
          - Dental Public Health Program, 1983 (Box 53)
          - Health Gerontology Program, 1983 (Box 54)
          - Human Nutrition Program, 1983 (Box 54)
        - Environmental and Industrial Health, 1981-1982; 2 folders (Box 54)
        - Epidemiology, 1981-1982; 2 folders (Box 54)
        - Health Behavior and Health Education, 1983-1984 (Box 54)
        - Health Planning and Administration, 1982-1983; 2 folders (Box 54)
        - Hospital Administration, 1982-1983; 3 folders (Box 54)
        - Medical Care Organization, 1982-1983; 2 folders (Box 54)
        - Population Planning, 1983-1984; 2 folders (Box 54)
      - Review Cycle, 1985
        - Hospital Administration, Medical Care Organization, Health Planning Administration, 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 54)
      - Review Cycle, 1987
        - Environmental and Industrial Health, 1987; 2 folders (Box 54)
  - Files, 1982-2005
    The 1982-2005 subseries of Office Files (11.7 linear feet) consists of records organized into seven sub-subseries: Budget, Collaborative Agreements, Committees, Reorganization, Enrollment, Miscellaneous, and Population Planning and International Health. The records in this subgroup were maintained separately from the dean's annual files and have been retained in the manner in which they were received. The activities of several different deans are represented in these files.
    - Council on Education for Public Health (CEPH) Accreditation